smithandcrown.com 2018-12-27

# Privacy Policy - Smith + Crown

This privacy policy applies to our collection, use, and processing of your personal data. Personal data is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personal Data in accordance with our website.

### What personal information do we collect from visitors to our website?

When registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address or other details to help you with your experience.

When submitting information to us via our Token Sale Questionnaire intake form, we will collect information including the name, email address, and project role of a technical contact and an interview contact.

### When do we collect information?

We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to a newsletter, or enter information on our site (eg. our Token Sale Questionnaire).

### How do we use your information?

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, visit our website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:  
• To personalize user’s experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.  
• To improve our website in order to better serve you.  
• To send periodic emails regarding new content and services.

If you submit information to us via our intake form, we may use that information to conduct proprietary research on your project. We will only ever publish publicly available information, which may include your name and your role within the project.

### How do we protect visitor information?

Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible.

We only provide articles and information. We never ask for personal or private information like credit card numbers.

### Do we use ‘cookies’?

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site’s or service provider’s systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we would use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart (if and when we offer items for sale on our site). They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

### We use cookies to:

• Understand and save user’s preferences for future visits.  
• Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third-party services that track this information on our behalf.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser’s Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.  
If you turn cookies off, some features will be disabled. It will disable some of the features that make your site experience experience more efficient and some of our services may not function properly.

### Third-party disclosure

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information unless we provide users with advance notice and obtain their consent. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or serving our users, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release information when its release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others’ rights, property, or safety.However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

### Third-party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

### Google Analytics

We use Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Alphabet Inc. (“Google”) to collect certain information relating to your use of our site. Google Analytics uses “cookies” to help analyze how our site is used. You can learn more about how Google uses data when using our site by visiting “How Google uses data when you use our partners’ sites or apps” (located at https://policies.google.com/privacy/partners).

### MailChimp

We use MailChimp to send out occasional marketing emails. You can learn more about how MailChimp uses data by viewing their privacy policy (located at https://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/).

### European Union General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)

The GDPR is a European Union regulation taking effect on May 25, 2018. The goal of GDPR is to improve the protections of “personal data.”

####  What we collect

We collect name, email address, job role, company name, website, location, description, IP address, date and time of first visit, data and time of last session, number of pageviews, and referral source that you may choose to provide to us. We may also collect other unsolicited personal information if you contact us or otherwise transmit it to us (e.g. in an email).

####  How we use and disclose your personal data

We use personal data to provide you with the Service as outlined in the Terms and Conditions of this website. Personal data is used to maintain the Service, understand how the Service is used, to monitor and protect the security of the Service, to analyze our business, and to communicate with you about the Service.

We may share personal data with other service providers (eg. Google Analytics and MailChimp) in order to help provide this Service, but only if they themselves are GDPR compliant. These service providers may only use this personal data in relation to helping us provide our Service.

#### Legal basis for processing your personal data

The legal bases for the processing of your personal data is (i) contract, (ii) your consent, and/or (iii) our legitimate interests to operate and improve our business. Where you have given consent to the processing of your personal data, you have the right to withdraw consent at any time.

####  Data subject rights

You have the right to request access, rectification, and deletion of your personal data held by us, and to receive a copy of your personal data in a structured machine-readable format. If you have created an account/profile on our site, you may at any time update, correct, or delete information you have provided us.

Where we have asked for your consent to process your data, you have the right to withdraw this consent at any time. Where we process your data because we have a legitimate interest in doing so, you have a right to object to this. These rights may be limited in certain situations, for example where there is a legal requirement to process your data.

If you wish you exercise your rights, you may contact us at privacy@smithandcrown.com with your request.

#### California Online Privacy Protection Act

CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law’s reach stretches well beyond California to require a person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting personally identifiable information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals with whom it is being shared, and to comply with this policy. – See more at: http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf

#### According to CalOPPA we agree to the following:

Users can visit our site anonymously.  
Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page or as a minimum on the first significant page after entering our website.  
Our Privacy Policy link includes the word ‘Privacy’ and can be easily be found on the page specified above.  
Users will be notified of any privacy policy changes:  
• On our Privacy Policy Page  
Users are able to change their personal information:  
• By logging in to their account  
• By emailing us at hello@smithandcrown.com with requested changes

### How does our site handle do not track signals?

We honor do not track signals and do not track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.

### Does our site allow third-party behavioral tracking?

It’s also important to note that we allow third-party behavioral tracking

### COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)

When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under 13, the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, the nation’s consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children’s privacy and safety online.

If you are under 13, please do not provide us with any personal information or attempt to register with our site. We do not specifically market to children under the age of 13 years old.

### Fair Information Practices

The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.  
In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:  
We will notify the users via email  
• Within 7 business days  
We also agree to the Individual Redress Principle, which requires that individuals have a right to pursue legally enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or government agencies to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.

### CAN SPAM Act

The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.  
We collect your email address in order to:  
• Send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.  
• Market to our mailing list.  
To be in accordance with CANSPAM we agree to the following:  
• NOT use false or misleading subjects or email addresses.  
• Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way.  
• Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters.  
• Monitor third-party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.  
• Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly.  
• Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email.

**If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can email us at** hello@smithandcrown.com and we will promptly remove you from **ALL** correspondence.

### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

privacy@smithandcrown.com  
United States  
Last Edited on 2018-05-24
